[{
  "front": "rozhodnutí",
  "back": "decision"
}, {
  "front": "konsenzus",
  "back": "consensus"
}, {
  "front": "domluva",
  "back": "agreement"
}, {
  "front": "obsazený",
  "back": "full"
}, {
  "front": "drobné",
  "back": "change"
}, {
  "front": "světlý",
  "back": "light"
}, {
  "front": "vztah",
  "back": "relationship"
}, {
  "front": "stín",
  "back": "shadow"
}, {
  "front": "chodník",
  "back": "sidewalk"
}, {
  "front": "značka",
  "back": "brand"
}, {
  "front": "nebezpečný",
  "back": "hazardous"
}, {
  "front": "zlý",
  "back": "evil"
}, {
  "front": "vítěz",
  "back": "winner"
}, {
  "front": "hlad",
  "back": "hungry"
}, {
  "front": "žízen",
  "back": "thirsty"
}, {
  "front": "zásoby",
  "back": "stock"
}, {
  "front": "mladší",
  "back": "younger"
}, {
  "front": "starší",
  "back": "older"
}, {
  "front": "těžké",
  "back": "difficult"
}, {
  "front": "vůbec",
  "back": "at all"
}]